Guide to the Yale Post-Doctoral Seminars on Education Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Post-doctoral Seminars on Education records
1957-1974
RU 475
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, schedules, and printed materials documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Post-doctoral Seminars on Education.
Yale Post-doctoral Seminars on Education
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, schedules, and printed materials documenting the activities and operations of the Yale Post-doctoral Seminars on Education.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Education -- Study and teaching; Seminars; Yale Post-doctoral Seminars on Education
- Records, Accession 1988-A-087
  - Correspondence, memoranda, meeting minutes, schedules and printed material
    - 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Directory, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)